[
    {
        "question": "Get me a glass of water",
        "words": {
          "4": "being",
          "1": "you",
          "3": "glass",
          "2": "asked",
          "5": "of",
          "6": "a",
          "7": "get",
          "8": "for",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "water",
          "11": "are",
          "12": "me"
        },
        "answers":[[1,11,2,9,7,12,6,3,5,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "May God bless you",
        "words": {
          "4": "God",
          "1": "be",
          "3": "you",
          "2": "blessed",
          "5": "by",
          "6": "may"
        },
        "answers":[[6,3,1,2,5,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Does tiger eat grass ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "grass",
          "1": "tiger",
          "3": "is",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "does",
          "6": "eaten",
          "7": "been"
        },
        "answers":[[3,4,6,2,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a doctor going to examine you ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "examined",
          "1": "gone",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "are",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "being",
          "8": "going",
          "9": "a",
          "10": "doctor",
          "11": "you"
        },
        "answers":[[2,11,8,5,3,4,6,9,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Have the police found the body ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "the body",
          "1": "the police",
          "3": "founded",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "has",
          "6": "found",
          "7": "the",
          "8": "is"
        },
        "answers":[[5,4,6,2,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shall I ever forget those happy days ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "happy",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "will",
          "5": "ever",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "days",
          "8": "been",
          "9": "forgotten",
          "10": "those"
        },
        "answers":[[2,10,1,7,3,5,9,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Did they catch the thief ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "was",
          "1": "did",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "thief",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "caught",
          "7": "the"
        },
        "answers":[[4,7,2,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did this ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "was",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "been",
          "5": "this",
          "6": "whom",
          "7": "done"
        },
        "answers":[[3,6,4,5,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did your sister write such a letter ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "letter",
          "1": "was",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "a",
          "5": "why",
          "6": "your",
          "7": "such",
          "8": "written",
          "9": "did",
          "10": "sister",
          "11": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[5,1,7,2,4,8,3,6,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Had you not seen the sky today ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "today",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "had",
          "2": "been",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "you",
          "7": "seen",
          "8": "not",
          "9": "sky"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,5,9,2,7,1,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is your mother going today ?",
        "words": {
          "4": "where",
          "1": "mother",
          "3": "is",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "being",
          "6": "your",
          "7": "gone",
          "8": "today",
          "9": "by"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    }
]